sp1: (Yamanaka) Eternal Boys The first step is sp1: Copy this completely
sp1: Post a video of yourself dancing.
(Asai) Dangerous! sp2: (Sanada) I'm sorry.
sp2: Ah... I'm sorry.
(Ishida) Ah...
Would you like to stop now? That kind of familiarity
(Imagawa) Huh?
I'm seriously here to become an idol.
sp2: quit everything
(Imagawa) Sanayan (Asai) Sanayan!
sp1: Sanada?
♬～
(Ishida) Um...
Would you like to start practicing again? (Asai) What about Sanayan?
(Ishida) Ah... (Imagawa) Mr. Ishida.
Is it because I said too much? (Ishida) I was just telling the truth.
Let's start again Mr. Yamanaka, okay?
sp1: Asai please play some music (Asai) Huh?
(Kakizaki) Manager, I don't think so.
Forcibly bring him here and then simply throw him away?
sp1: Look for a replacement responsibly
sp1: There's no problem with that.
From a while ago, is that the company's opinion?
I'd like to talk to Mr. Yamanaka.
sp1: Let's restart
sp1: From the head
sp1: １ ２ １ ２ ３
sp2: Delivering love to the table sp2: Strongly attracted to the corporate philosophy
sp2: I applied
sp2: Being in a sales position also means sp2: past knowledge and experience
sp2: I think it can be put to good use.
(Interviewer) By the way...
What have you done in the period since you left your previous company?
sp2: Um...
sp2: A little part-time job in customer service
sp2: Yes, second interview?
sp2: Please let me participate
sp2: Yes thank you
sp2: Yes, excuse me.
♬～
(Level crossing warning sound)
(Asai) Ei Ho (Imagawa) Oh
Hehehe (Imagawa) As expected.
Ima-chan Ima-chan Hey (Ishida) Hey!
Please don't play soccer indoors!
(Asai) Sorry, sorry, it's just a habit. (Imagawa) Hehe, what kind of habit?
(Asai) Please do it outside.
Eihoi Hoihoi
(Asai) Hey
(Imagawa) It hurts hahahaha (Asai) Ei
⚞(Asai) Hoi Hoi ⚞(Imagawa) Hoi
⚞(Asai) Hey, hey ⚞(Imagawa) Hey
⚞(Imagawa) Hoi⚞(Akai) Hoi
(sound of door opening)
sp1: Are you back?
sp2: No, I just came to pick up my luggage...
sp2: Also...
sp2: this
sp2: As expected...
sp2: Life is sp2: You can't change it easily.
sp2: Sorry
sp2: It was a short time, but sp2: Thank you for your help.
sp1: I see.
sp1: Got it
sp1: Ah (Kakizaki) That's about it.
sp1: Huh?
sp1: I can't sleep without this
If you can't sleep, it's good to drink something warm.
sp1: More than alcohol? than alcohol
sp1: He can change it.
sp1: He said he would change it...
sp1: Was it my mistake in judgment again?
♬～
(Manager) Oh, wait, it's a product.
Hey, be a little more gentle... (Part-time job) Ah, I understand.
(Manager) I understand by arranging them neatly like this.
(Manager) If there's anything you don't understand, please let me know.
sp2: Yes (manager) Yes.
♬～
(Part-time job) Ah, Dali
(Part-time job) He seems serious.
sp2: Ah, it's normal.
(Part-time job) Well then, I'm going to take a break.
sp2: Huh...
♬～
(Part-time job) Ah...
asleep
Well then, it's time sp2: Thank you for your hard work.
(Sound of door opening and closing)
(Manager) Thank you for your hard work sp2: Ah, thank you for your hard work.
(Manager) If you want something, please bring it as many as you want.
sp2: Eh, is that okay? (Manager) Of course
Thanks to Sanada-kun, today I can go home without overtime for the first time in a while.
sp2: Not at all I don't have anything... No, no.
Because kids these days are a little different.
You complain easily and run away right away, right?
(Manager) Well, there are people like that no matter where you go.
It's not going well though
⚟♬ “Shall we dance?” ”
sp2: Gentlemen?
♬～
Sanada
sp2: Mr. Kakizaki, what are you doing?
(Kakizaki) Are you planning on not coming back?
sp2: sp2: I'm sure things will go better without me.
sp2: I have a normal job
sp2: return to normal life
Is that okay?
sp2: Mr. Kakizaki doesn't understand.
(Kakizaki) Is that so? sp2: To the person who has always been chosen
sp2: There's no way you can understand the feelings of those who are always not chosen sp2:
Do I look like... chosen?
sp2: yes
sp2: Well...
(Kakizaki) Sanada!
Look carefully
Ishida is also a dance beginner like Sanada.
But Ishida sneaks out of the training camp every night.
I'm practicing here
I also have this kind of skin that I always pack every day...
(Kakizaki) Don't make decisions just based on what you see.
(Kakizaki) Or if I'm not looking.
If Sanada is trying hard too, I apologize.
sp2: Me too...
sp2: It doesn't matter to me anymore.
I'm sure it's what attracts people
Those who have not been chosen are better than those who have been chosen.
What lies beyond that
It's a story that can only be written because it's not special.
sp2: It's never too late now...
Because it seems like anyone can shine anytime.
♬～
sp2: That's sp2: Isn't it all beautiful?
sp1: Sanada wasn't suitable
sp1: That's all.
♬～
(Kakizaki) Let's continue!
sp1: our debut song
sp1: The title is "Eternal"
(Imagawa) Kita sp1: If the debut song has been decided
sp1: What I need to do next is sp1: That's it after all.
(Ren) The old man's MV is too lame.
sp2: I'm an idol sp2: I'll try really hard